clovenetwork.com 2013-06-21

# Clove Network | Delivering measurable reach

**Clove Network is deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users.**

Accordingly, we strictly adhere to all industry guidelines, and will continue to review and improve our privacy policy and procedures to ensure the safety and protection of consumer information. This Privacy Statement presents our privacy policy, including Clove Network privacy practices for our web site. Below is information regarding Clove Network commitment to protecting the privacy of Internet users. 

Consumer Information

Clove Network uses one or more third party ad serving technology to serve ads at this site and at our clients' sites. In the course of delivering an ad to you, the third party ad serving party may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser and use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this non-personally-identifiable information used to serve ads to you, please [click here.](http://ad.yieldmanager.com/opt-out)

Cookies and Opt Out

Like most Internet sites, Clove Network and its third party ad serving party use "cookies" to enhance the Internet user's experience on the Web. Neither Clove Network nor such third party ad serving party use these cookies to personally identify you in any way, and these cookies in no way damage your system or files. 

Cookies and Web Beacons

We use persistent "cookies" on this Website in order to help us manage the opt-out process for our Platform. For information on our opt-out process, please review the section of this privacy policy entitled "Opting out from Cookies" below. Cookies are small text files that contain a string of alphanumeric characters. Web beacons (also known as "1X1 pixels" or "clear GIFs") are small strings of code that provide a method for delivering a graphic image on a web page or in an email message for the purpose of transferring data. For more information about cookies and web beacons please visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/>

Cookies and Web beacons

Our Clients use cookies in conjunction with Web beacons when they use the Platform in order to help make the online advertisements you see more relevant to you. We also use cookies and Web beacons (under the domain adnxs.com) to help our clients make advertising more relevant. We also use cookies and web beacons for ad delivery and reporting purposes, to measure the success of our Clients' online advertising campaigns. 

Opting out from Cookies

If you'd like to opt-out from having AppNexus collect your Non-PII in connection with our Platform, please [click here](http://ib.adnxs.com/optout). When you opt out, we will place an opt-out cookie on your computer. The opt-out cookie tells us not to collect your Non-PII to help us tailor our Clients' online advertisement campaigns. Please note that if you delete, block or otherwise restrict cookies, or if you use a different computer or Internet browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice. 

What are cookies and how do they enhance your Web experience?

A cookie is a unique number that is assigned to you the first time you are served an ad. This number is stored in a file on your computer. For instance, cookies help ensure that you don't repeatedly see the same ad. Cookies can also help advertisers measure how you utilize an advertiser's site and the effectiveness of an ad. This information can then be used by advertisers to better cater to your needs. In other words, cookies help us deliver to you the types of ads in which you are more interested. 

Although we believe that cookies help enhance your experience on the Web (by not repeatedly serving the same ads to you and delivering more relevant messages to you), neither Clove Network nor its third party ad serving party needs cookies to deliver ads to you. 

Opt Out

If you do not want the benefits of cookies, there is a simple procedure that allows you to deny or accept this feature. In order to "opt out" of the benefits of cookies, you may either manually delete your cookies by following the instructions contained in the Help section of your browser, or you may [click here.](http://ad.yieldmanager.com/opt-out)

Industry Efforts to Protect Consumer Privacy

Clove Network is committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Accordingly, we strictly adhere to all industry guidelines, including those established by the Direct Marketing Association. To review information regarding privacy practices on our Clove Network Web site, please [click here](http://www.clovenetwork/). If you should have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, please contact our Customer Services at [info@Clovenetwork.com](mailto:info@clovenetwork.com) . We recommend that you periodically review this Privacy Statement, as Clove Network may update it from time to time. 

Third Party Advertising

We use Clove Network , and other third-party advertising companies, to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here.](http://ad.yieldmanager.com/opt-out)

Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.
